* * * Subtitles by dylux * * *
( Squeaking )
♪ ( " Show Me The Way To Go Home " on radio ) ♪
♪ ( Man sings along drunkenly ) ♪
( Grunts )
( Bottles clink )
♪ Wherever I may roam ♪
♪ On land or sea or foam ♪
♪ You can always hear me singin ' this song ♪
- ♪ Show me the way to go home ♪ - ( Knocks on boat )
♪ I 'm tired and I want to go to bed ♪
♪ I had a little drink about an hour ago and it went ... ♪
( Grunts )
Oh , boy , that 's a fast fish .
Come on . Come on ! Come on !
Look at that ! You big son of a bitch !
( Rumbling )
( Tremors )
Ohh !
Ahh !
Aargh !
Oh ! Help ! Aargh !
( Moans )
MAN ON RADIO : Oh , yeah it 's the Wave 88.1 , and the quiet before the storm has passed
and Spring Break has arrived to Lake Victoria !
The next few days , all 25 square miles of our beautiful lake
is gonna be covered in babes , boats and bikinis !
So , if you felt the earth move this morning , it wasn 't just the party .
Seems like Lake Vic was the center of a light quake .
So , if you see some scientist types out there on the lake , hand them a cold one .
♪ Just like my nano ♪
♪ She 's shufﬂin ' it , I 'm lovin ' it ♪
♪ I 'm thinking about touchin ' it ♪
♪ Kissin ' her in public ♪
♪ But baby got me fumblin ' ♪
♪ Stumblin ' and mumblin ' ♪
♪ And plus she got me wonderin ' ♪
♪ If I should get her number then ♪
♪ She just looked up at me and said ♪
♪ Take me in the bathroom ♪
♪ Take my clothes off ♪
♪ Make love to me up against a dirty wall ♪
- ♪ ' Cause I can 't wait to get you home - Wait to get you home ♪
♪ She tastes like cigarettes and alcohol ♪
♪ Up all night on Adderall ♪
♪ Innocent , but not at all ♪
♪ She my Brooklyn Barbie doll ♪
- ♪ Dancin ' like ... - Mm ! ♪
- ♪ Thinkin ' like ... - Ooh ! ♪
♪ What you think about sex on the first night ? Mm , okay ♪
♪ I 'm thinking about touchin ' it ♪
♪ Kissin ' her in public ♪
♪ But baby got me fumblin ' , ♪
♪ Stumblin ' and mumblin ' ♪
♪ And plus she got me wonderin ' ♪
- ♪ If I should get her number then - Say ho ! ♪
♪ I just looked at her instead and I said ... ♪
Officer , it was a mistake . Can 't we just work something out here ?
Mistake or no mistake , you destroyed public property ,
and from the smell of your breath , I suggest you take the ticket ,
get a ride home with your friends .
I was kinda hoping you might drive me home .
Touching an officer 's uniform is considered assault ... were you aware of that ?
Come on , you look pretty hot in tan .
Oh !
It 's not tan , it 's beige .
- ( Groans ) - Think you could take it easy on him ?
If you boys take one more step , you 'll be pissing lightning bolts into next week , okay ?
♪ Shake , shake Do your thing , do your thing ♪
♪ Shake , shake Come on , bang it , bang it ♪
- ♪ Shake , shake , come on , baby ♪ - MAN : Hey , hey !
- ♪ Shake , shake , do your thing ... ♪ - Whoo-hoo !
Yeah , it 's pretty much your average day in college .
Kelly , hey !
I wasn 't sure you were coming back ... for Spring Break .
Yeah , I 'm ... I 'm here . ( Laughs )
I can only assume that you 're down here to get on one of those boats .
No , no , I came down to pick up my little sister from her music lessons .
How about yourself ?
I 'm waiting for my ride . Todd and his friends , we 're gonna go check out some music .
Todd Dupree ?
Remind me who you 're going out with again ?
I have standards , all right ? That 's all I 'm saying .
Todd 's a really good DJ .
Kelly ! Let 's go . Jump in , we 're late .
He says he 's got backstage passes for Planters , you should come .
Yeah , I would , but I 'm pretty much under house arrest watching Zane and Laura .
Too bad .
- We 'll miss you . - ( Car horn )
- I gotta go . - Come on , let 's go !
Yeah , hopefully I see you again before you ...
before you leave . Way to make a move , Jake .
Hey-hey , ass wipe !
Cool shirt !
Nice horn .
Thanks .
Nice boobs .
I have a training bra but I don 't like to wear it because it itches .
Tell me about it .
Who you waiting for ?
My brother , Jake . He 's 17 . ( Hushed ) He 'll like your boobs too .
- They all do . - Come on , Laura , let 's go .
- What happened to you ? - I don 't wanna talk about it . Let 's go .
Hi , Jake .
- Try not to stare at her boobs . - Shut up !
- ( Laughs ) I like your shirt . - You wanna throw something at me too ?
No , actually , I like the Pixies .
Danni , Danni , Danni , where the hell is Crystal ?
Over there with Andrew . They 're getting sunscreen . I 'm just waiting .
Sunscreen ? Andrew , Crystal , we don 't need sunscreen , we need body paint ,
we need condoms and Redi-Whip . You tell her 10am tomorrow ,
I want her bleached blond booty at the marina .
Gotta get my first shot off by noon , so bright and early , baby ,
make sure those titties are nice and perky ! Mm , ha !
Who 's this ?
This is Jake . He 's a local .
A sand rat , huh ? D 'you know your way around the lake ?
- Yeah . - D 'you want a job ? I pay cash money .
Don 't bullshit me , Jake . My guy didn 't show and I need somebody ASAP ,
somebody I can rely on , somebody with ambition ,
someone who 's willing to take chances , if you know what I mean .
Mister , you talk funny .
- Yeah , well , you 're short . - ( Ringtone )
Hold on . This is Derrick .
Oh , no , no , no , don 't you disappoint me , motherfucker .
I told you , I want the biggest goddamn boat this podunk town has to offer . Hold on .
Who is that ?
Derrick ? He 's the director .
Oh , so are you like a ... an actress or what ?
I 'm a wild , wild girl .
... big boat , with a big motor .
What 's a wild , wild girl , Jake ?
Of course we know boats ! No , fuck the waiver , you sign the waiver !
- So , Jake , baby , we gonna do this ? - Do ?
The job . Location scout . Guide us around , show us all the good spots , the G-spots .
I need a local . I need you .
We 're talking life lesson here , Jake .
Great , 10 am tomorrow .
Don 't be late and ... wear a different shirt .
- I guess we 'll see you tomorrow , Jake . - Actually , tomorrow he 's ...
( Laughs )
- ( Knock on door ) - Jake .
Why you gonna knock if you 're just gonna walk in ?
Am I disturbing you ?
No , I 'm just doing homework and schoolwork and research for school .
Laura has been telling me that you may have some other plans for tomorrow .
No , what 's she talking about ? I 'm 100 % babysitting .
What ? No , we don 't want a babysitter !
- Yeah , Mom , especially not Jake . - ( Mimics ) Especially not Jake .
I 'm serious , we don 't need ...
- No , get out . Out . Out ! - No , please , Mom .
Mom , please , we have to talk about this .
- Mom ! - Jake , you know I do not have a backup .
Yeah , I know , Mom . Don 't worry .
I know how crazy this week is for you , and I 'll take care of the nitwits , okay ?
Remember , if you do not fulfill your responsibility ,
I have the power to arrest and imprison you .
I 'm not 12 . Playing the sheriff card isn 't gonna work any more .
- No ? - No .
Like I said , I 'll take care of it , okay ?
All right . You better .
Get outta here .
- Next year I 'll try to find another solution . - All right .
- All right ? - Okay .
( sighs ) Fuck .
- ( Beep ) - ( Moaning )
- Oh , and Jake ... - Oh , Mom , come on ! Really ?
- It 's time for dinner , - All right , I 'll be right there .
( Beep )
- Hope I didn 't wake the kids . - Oh , God , they 'll sleep through anything .
Maggie said that yesterday was the last time she saw him ?
Yeah , just before noon .
She said Matt took the boat out to catch some bass .
She drove around the lake all night looking for him .
- Where 's the boat ? - Over there .
( Pier creaks )
MAN : Feeling like a skinny dip ?
( Woman laughs ) I think we can make it to the end of the pier .
MAN : Meaning what - I 'm too old or too heavy ?
WOMAN : I think you 're too chickenshit . ( Laughs )
- MAN : By the way , Gordon called last night . - Yeah ?
He said the USGS recorded heavy seismic activity beneath the lake .
Really ?
They 're sending in a team of seismologist divers .
All right .
And he told them that you 're gonna escort them out .
Jesus Christ !
I 've just been invaded by 20,000 kids - makes us a little busy at the moment .
- That 's what I told him . - ( Pier creaking and cracking )
This doesn 't sound too good .
So , what time are the divers gonna get here ?
They said by ten .
( Grunts )
Shit !
Come on , just a little more .
Oh , I can 't get it .
Oh !
Jules !
Gimme your hand !
( Gasps , screams )
JULIE : Do you think a propeller could have done this ?
I doubt it . Look at the bones , nothing 's broken .
It 's like something acidic , or toxic decomposition ,
as if this body 's been in the water for weeks .
What would you say if I told you that I 'm thinking about closing the lake ?
Just until we get an autopsy report .
An autopsy report is gonna take a couple of days .
It 'd be easier to drain this lake than to close it .
It 's a big financial week for our town .
I 'm too old for this .
Whoo-hoo !
Aargh ! Aargh !
Aargh !
( Muffled chatter )
- We 're not lying to Mom . - Yeah , we 're not lying to Mom .
Every year it 's the same thing ,
I 'm stuck here with you guys while I miss all the Spring Break fun .
- You mean Spring Break boobies . - What if I give you the babysitting cash ?
- 60 bucks and you got a deal . - 60 ? I 'm only getting paid 40 !
$ 20 deception surcharge .
Do not pick up the phone , do not answer the door ,
and do not leave the house .
Okay ? I 'm counting on you guys . All right ?
♪ Fetish for these kicks , fetish for these jeans ♪
♪ A fetish for my hoody ♪
♪ Fetish , fetish , fetish ♪
Town rules , son .
Toss a piece of trash in our lake , you gotta pick up ten pieces .
- You want me to pick up these bottles ? - Pick ' em up !
None of these fuckers pick anything up !
Hey ! After the dive , our presence is requested at Kokomo 's
by the Arizona State cheerleading team .
Hi , I 'm Sheriff Forester . Bob Gordon asked me to take you out to the site .
Good to meet you . I like the welcoming committee here .
- I assume that 's technical equipment too ? - Sam , give those back . Come on .
According to the epicenter co-ordinates ,
we need to go ... here .
Okay . That 's about 20 minutes out .
- Ready when you are . - All right .
You don 't see many women working law enforcement out here in cowboy country .
- I see a lot of cowboys though . - I 'm sure .
( Dance music )
( Cheering )
♪ Bring the noise ! ♪
Yeah , baby , take it off !
- Whoo ! - Baby , I 'll do anything !
Yeah , baby ! Yeah ! Love you !
- Whoo ! - Yeah !
♪ I see you chillin ' by the bar ♪
♪ Why don 't you grab your girls and come chill with a star ? ♪
♪ Yeah , up in VIP , drinks on me ♪
♪ Swag on tight with a gangsta lean ♪
♪ Everybody know just who I are ... ♪
( All chant ) Motorboat , motorboat , motorboat , motorboat , motorboat !
Motorboat , motorboat , motorboat !
- Yeah ! - ( Cheering )
♪ They can drink a lil ' mo They can drink a lil ' mo ♪
♪ Oh , you don 't hear me though ? ♪
Whoo , yeah !
- Kelly ! - Jake !
- Uh ... - Who exactly are you babysitting here ?
Well , it 's a funny story , actually ...
DERRICK : I 'll say " tit " , you say " ies " !
- Tit ! - ALL : .. ies !
- Tit ! - ies !
Wow ! Wow ! Look at those idiots !
It 's , uh , terrible .
Sand rat !
Hey , sand rat , I 'm talking to you ! Sand rat ! Hello !
Where you been ? We got the girls lubed up , we 're ready to roll !
I 'm docking your pay check . Come on , let 's go !
Jake ?
Now I see what you 've been scouting the last 15 minutes .
Kelly , it was great to see you , I know you gotta get going .
Kelly ! Kelly , hi , I 'm Derrick Jones .
Hi .
- You know this guy ? - Who , Jake ?
Jake is my boy .
Jake is the man with the plan , the insight , the knowledge .
Wait ... those girls aren 't with you , are they ?
Uh , yeah . Why , are you into girls ?
No , I 'm just showing him around town , just all the hot spots and stuff like that .
Jake , the job is called " location scout " , and Kelly , you should come with .
Today we 're gonna be making movie history .
She 's got other plans already .
Kelly , do you like champagne ?
I ... I love champagne !
- Actually ... - No , no , no , no , wait ...
I would love to come on your boat , Derrick , thank you .
Someone has to keep an eye on the man with the plan here , right ?
Come on , come on , let me ... let me help you aboard .
Why ? Why ?
Dude , that 's Kelly .
Kelly ! Baby ?
What happened to hanging with us today ?
- Is that your boyfriend ? - No , he 's just some guy from school .
Someone who says he has backstage passes when he doesn 't .
- Have a good day , Todd . - Come on , Kelly !
Yo , have a t-shirt .
- What the fuck ? - That was Derrick Jones !
Is that Jake Forester ?
Oh , fuck it !
We are off to shoot some wildcore blow-your-mind footage ,
with these wild , wild goddesses !
- ( All cheer ) - Yeah !
We will see you all , four o 'clock , Canyon Beach ,
for the Lake Victoria wet T-shirt
- wild extravaganza ! - ( Cheering )
Zane , we have to talk about this . We told Jake we 'd stay at the house .
I told him I 'd fish ,
and I can 't if there aren 't any .
The lake 's too busy .
Come on , Sand Island 's really close .
I should have brought my trombone .
No way , be a girl and just sunbathe or something .
Well , when I become a rock star , see if I let you be one of my groupies .
Gimme a break , dude ! You play the trombone !
♪ ( Loud dance music ) ♪
DERRICK : Ladies , here we go ,
- a little bubbly . - Thank you .
- It 's the finest your gas station has to offer . - ( Laughter )
- ( Laughter ) - There we go . Drink up , Crystal .
- Yay ! - Enjoy and cheers .
- Cheers . - To our newest wild , wild member .
- ( All laugh ) - You are beautiful .
That 's why we came here . Derrick wants to capture innocence .
He says it 's all about innocence .
Like her .
Don 't worry , Derrick 's just making his play . You might as well ask him not to breathe .
Drew 's rules ... show a girl a camera and she will perform .
It 's like a law of physics . I 've seen that guy charm the pants off a lot of ladies .
She 's not messing up your party , is she ?
Like I care , she 's not my girlfriend . No , and ...
I 'm ... This is great , I 'm having a great time , we 're going wild , I 'm ... I 'm going wild .
Hey , Jake , how far is this place ? Come on !
Yeah , yeah , we 're almost there .
So speaking of going wild
you haven 't seen anything yet .
( Laughs )
Jake ! Jake !
Yeah ?
( Both laugh )
Jake !
( Laughs )
Why don 't you put it somewhere ? ( Laughs )
Anywhere you want . Anywhere you want , baby .
Crystal , leave her alone , she 's not even legal .
♪ ( Delibes Lakme 's " Flower Duet " ) ♪
- What 's up , guys ? - Close that door ! You 're ruining our shot !
Come on , sand rat , get with the program here .
Here they come , here they come , here come my nymphs . ( Laughs )
( Laughs ) Oh , my God !
Here we go .
Check it out , it 's like fish with boobies . ( Laughs )
If fish looked like that , I would fuck fish , I would only fuck fish !
- ( Both laugh ) - Here we go .
Looking good , ladies . You like this , right , Jake ?
You should be paying us today , not the other way around .
Zoom in , zoom , zoom , zoom , zoom in .
Get that ass .
( Laughs ) Look at these goddess aquatic bitches .
This is hot , Andy , this is so hot , this is what it 's all about .
Beer , sun and naked honeys making out underwater .
- Boom ! - ( All laugh )
( Phone rings )
Better than any aquarium you 've been to , sand rat !
Mom .
- Uh , Mom , hey ... - Mom ?
- What 's going on over there ? - Ooh , naked bitches !
How come you didn 't pick up the home phone ? I 've been trying to reach you .
- ( Laughter ) - I 'm sorry , we 've been outside , but I can ...
- Crystal , spin around ! - ... I can go get them .
JULIE : No , that 's okay .
JAKE : Oh , my God !
What ?
Oh , nothing , nothing . It 's just the kids , they just pitched the tent outside and I ...
It 's really nice to see them ... to see them playing with each other .
- Put your ass on the glass ! - Put your ass on the glass , yeah !
Your chocha !
Jake , is someone there with you ?
No , no , no , it 's just the kids out on the lake , it 's crazy here . You know how it is .
Honey , I do not want Zane or Laura near the lake today , do you hear me ?
All right , okay , we 'll stay in , we 'll watch some TV , whatever 's on , okay ?
Mom : All right , I gotta go . Thank you so much for this .
I 'll try really hard to be home early , okay ?
Yeah , all right , all right , I love you . Okay , I gotta go .
Kelly ?
Kelly , where are you ?
- ( Laughter ) - Jake !
You just missed the rest of the big show .
There you go , girls , come on up , give ' em some towels .
Wow , good work . Way to tie off a canoe .
I must have gotten my knots mixed up .
So , you catch zero fish and you lose our only boat .
This day is just full of accomplishments . Jake is gonna kill us .
Somebody will see us . Look , there 's some boats just right over there .
Don 't waste your time .
They 'll never see us , they 're way too far .
Hello !
Hey !
Hey ! Help !
We need some help !
Hey , we 're over here !
Somebody please help us !
Please ! Help !
Help !
Hey , we need help !
Please !
Please ! Help !
Hey !
Please !
Ow ! Oh !
Ah !
( Beeping )
Whoa , look at the size of that . What is it , a cavern system ?
Looks to me like a subterranean lake , probably bigger than the one above .
WOMAN : Sam , can you gimme a hand over here ?
- See that gap there ? - Yeah .
The quake opened that up , now it 's a connecting passage .
A lake under a lake ?
That 's right . Sorry , it 's still your jurisdiction .
This is part of an old volcanic ridge all over this area .
That 's the beauty of it . We 're gonna be the first ones to explore it .
I don 't know why you 're getting all excited about that crap .
All we ever see is rocks and sand .
Should probably warn them that it 's not very pretty down there .
Tourists treat this lake like it 's a garbage can .
How you guys doing ? Sheriff says it 's a regular treasure trove down there , so ...
I got dibs on the spent bottles of Axe body spray and back issues of Jugs .
WOMAN : I got dibs on home appliances .
SAM : I got dibs on missing college girls .
WOMAN : Oh , my God !
This is the longest one I 've ever seen .
MAN : Can you keep your mind on the task at hand ?
( Woman laughs ) Wow , Sam .
It 's at least 200 feet , Novak .
Almost full visibility .
SAM : Descending fissure . My PO2 is at set point 1.3 .
WOMAN : You should see this , it 's unbelievable .
SAM : Novak , do you copy ?
NOVAK : Yeah , pretty good .
Okay , guys , you 're about 90 feet to the entrance of the connecting passage .
SAM : Looks like single file time .
I 'll go first .
WOMAN : No , I should do the prelim scout . Your fat ass will get us stuck .
SAM : Baby , I 'm like an eel , an electric eel .
I get into such tight spaces it 's shocking .
- ( Beeping ) - Huh , that 's weird .
Here they are , but they 're splitting up .
Guys , everything all right ? I 'm losing you a little bit here .
SAM : I 'm hitting a serious drop in temperature . It 's at least 30 degrees colder .
WOMAN : You 're probably at the mouth of the underwater lake .
Do you have any visual ?
MAN : I 'm entering the cave .
Jesus , this thing seems endless !
You gotta see this . This is incredible .
Fuck !
WOMAN : What are you seeing down there ?
Sam ?
Something bit me !
( Woman laughs ) Oh , yeah , right . I thought you always liked that kind of stuff .
- Sam ? Sam ? - ( Distorted audio signal )
- Answer me ! Sam ! ? - ( Sam screams )
Sam !
Something 's happening .
- An aftershock ? - I don 't know . Get me my flippers .
Fucking swim !
( Gasps ) Oh no !
( Screams ) Fucking swim ! No !
( Screams ) No !
( Screams )
Get him out of the water !
Get him out !
- Oh , fuck ! - Oh !
Oh , my God !
♪ ( Ozomatli 's " Nadas Por Free " ) ♪
- ( Cheering ) - Ah-ha-ha !
- ( Laughs ) - Ladies .
( All laugh )
Your body is a temple and now it 's time to give thanks to the gods .
Mm .
Andrew , roll camera .
- Kelly , you 're up . - No , no , no , no , no .
No , thanks , I think I 've already had too much .
You don 't wanna worship at this beautiful altar ?
I know you 're partial to the champagne , but , believe us , you can trust Crystal , right .
- Come on , Derrick , she said no . - No , she said " no , thanks " .
There 's a difference . She understands gratitude is the right attitude .
Kelly , Kelly , trust us , it 's never cheating if it 's with another chick .
- Come on ! - Have fun , do it . Everyone 's doin ' it .
- You 're not trying to take away her fun ? - Like I said , she 's , uh ...
she 's not my girlfriend .
Fine .
- I 'll do it . - Okay .
Okay , here we go .
- First you lick the salt , here we go . - Okay .
Come on over here .
Then you suck up the tequila .
- ( Cheering ) - Here we go .
Sorry about that , Crystal .
And your vitamin C , you gotta get your lime .
- Body temple . - Kelly , you don 't have to do this .
I don 't think we need any of your babysitting here , Jake .
- Ho-ho-ho ! Facial ! - Whoo !
( Shudders )
Okay .
♪ She looked me up and down ♪
♪ She said , " You gots to have the mettle to take me out on town " ♪
♪ I said , " Chillax , baby girl , gimme ten for my motor " ♪
♪ She smiled in my face ... ♪ - Yeah !
- ( Danni laughs ) - Jake , I bet you wish that was you .
You got a sand rat making out with the model .
- I bet you wish that was your job . - ( Both laugh )
All right , all right , all right , all right , let 's switch places .
- Great job , Kelly . Jake , you 're up . - Let 's mix it up a little bit .
- How about we try Jake and Kelly ? - ( Both ) What ? No , I don 't think ...
Come on , Derrick .
Come on , guys , we 're shooting porno , not a drama . Make a decision , come on .
Come on .
Fuck it , sand rats , let 's roll , come on .
There you go , thank you , Crystal . Come on , Kelly . Come on .
Come on , right there .
- There we go . - Whoo !
Let 's get you salt .
A little bit of te-kill-ya .
- ( Giggles ) - Okay , yeah .
And ... your lime .
Okay , roll , roll , roll . Go .
( Beep )
( Laughs )
( All ) Sand rat , sand rat , sand rat , sand rat , sand rat , sand rat , sand rat .
- ( Laughs ) - Sand rat , sand rat , sand rat , sand rat .
Sand rat , sand rat , sand rat , sand rat .
Ohh !
( Banging )
JULIE : Mr. Goodman !
Mr. Goodman !
( Banging )
- I 'm coming . - ( Banging )
I 'm coming ! Hold your horses !
The store is closed !
I wanna know what the hell this thing is doing in my lake .
Where did you get this ?
In the middle of the lake , where there are two people dead .
( Grunts )
Oh !
- Oh my ! - Oh my , that 's right , oh my , oh my !
Excuse me , but ... is that a fucking piranha ?
- Carl ? - It 's not the only one .
Here , look at this . There are thousands of ' em .
Thousands . And they 're pissed .
I 've heard of this happening . It 's like those baby alligators in New Jersey ,
- someone leaves them , then they breed . - What ?
- No one released this fish into the lake . - What are you talking about ?
This particular piranha vanished off the face of the earth
more than two million years ago .
Where 's he going ?
Oh .
Allow me to introduce you ...
( Groans )
to pygocentrus nattereri , the original piranha .
They used to swim the Colorado River right up until the Pleistocene Epoch .
I still don 't understand how you found one
alive .
We discovered a subterranean lake through a rift caused by the quake .
But , how could it have survived for so long cut off from the surface ?
Cannibalism .
They must have fought each other to survive . Look .
All the scars on his scales .
Notice ... the eyes .
Jesus , it 's like he 's staring back at you .
Oh , no , no , no , no , not staring .
Sensing .
- Oh God ! - God , don 't do that !
Piranha hunt in packs ,
not for protection , but for overwhelming force .
They 're organized , methodical .
The first bite draws blood . The blood draws the pack .
So , how are we going to stop them ?
You 're not actually considering going back out onto the lake ?
They 're killing machines but they 're still fish , you can catch them or kill them .
- But if there really are thousands ... - Yeah ?
yesterday would have been a good time to start .
( Screaming )
- ( Screaming ) - Whoo !
Yeah !
- Whoa ! - ♪ Oh , baby , yeah ♪
♪ If you want the love of a man , come and get it ♪
♪ All right , now ♪
- ♪ If you want the love ... ♪ - ( Screams )
♪ Of a real good man ♪
♪ Come on inside me I 'll make you understand ♪
- Yeah ! - ♪ Don 't just look ♪
♪ Come on and take it ♪
♪ ' Cause what I 've got , you know that you can 't fake it ♪
♪ ' Cause if you want the love of a man , come and get it ♪
♪ Oh , if you want the love of a man , you got to get with it ♪
♪ So , if you want the love of a man , come and get it ♪
♪ Oh , if you want the love of a man , you gotta get with it , listen ♪
♪ Remember , girl , I been around the block ♪
♪ My legs are tired but I wont stop ♪
♪ Now it 's your turn to make a choice ♪
♪ Don 't just sit there , girl , stand up and raise your voice ... ♪
Oh , shit !
It 's my little brother and sister .
Are they waving for help ?
I don 't know , they 're supposed to be at home right now .
- I 'm supposed to be at home right now . - What are you doing ?
- You 're gonna miss my money shot . - It 's my family , they could be in trouble .
You are gonna be the one who 's in trouble if I don 't get my flying ta-tas right now !
What the hell is wrong with you , man ?
- What 's wrong with me ? - Girl : Yeah !
Goddamn it , you 're missing it , you 're missing the shot !
( Screams )
No , no , no , no . You missed it ! What is wrong with you ?
Listen , they 're stranded out there , okay ?
They might need my help .
Boobies , boobies , boobies .
Listen to me , my mom is the sheriff .
LAURA : Hey , we need help over here !
LAURA : Hello ?
LAURA : Help me !
All right , let 's ... swing by the island .
Throw the minnows in the boat . ( Laughs )
It 'll be great . It 'll be fun .
( Screams ) Take me up !
- Yeah ! - Whoo !
( Gasps )
- ( Girl screams ) - Yeah !
( Screams )
- Help me ! - She 's not joking .
- Take me up ! - What the hell 's going on ?
♪ ( Honorebel 's " Now You See It " ) ♪
All right , Lake Victoria , ready for some titties ?
- ( Cheering ) - Yeah !
Now it 's time for another episode of The Hills ! Yeah !
I 'm talking about titties , ladies .
Look at those weapons of masturbation right over here !
Let 's see those jugs . All right , girls .
Use it , yeah , shake the booty , girls .
Shake it like Willy Wonka and the chocolate factory .
We 're gonna crack open those coconuts and drink from God 's milk jugs !
Get the girls out , let 's see them , what are you hiding under there ?
Come on , baby , let 's see those summer tomatoes . Let 's see those ta-tas .
Show me those Danny DeVitos .
Come on , girls , let 's take a bite out of those cutie Klondikes , yeah .
I need the National Guard . I need the Coastguard .
I need all the forces in your power to deploy .
- Come on , girls ... - Everybody back to the beach !
Take your boats back to the dock , everybody .
- We need you to clear out . - Please clear out now .
MC : Come on girls , let 's see the titties , all right ?
Yeah ! The fun bags !
Let 's see those Brad Pitts . Let 's see Bonnie and Clyde !
- The Bible will save you ! - Satan is coming !
Don 't talk about Satan , just take your boat back .
No more talk about Satan . Please !
Cut the engine .
( Gunshots )
What the fuck ?
This is the Lake Victoria Sheriff 's Department .
The sheriff has declared an emergency .
Don 't worry , we got beer over here !
( Cheering )
- Hey , get up outta there . - ( Cheering )
I need you out of the water now !
Yeah ! Hit it , DJ Chocolate Thunder !
♪ ( Loud dance music ) ♪
( Cheering )
Whoo !
Yeah !
♪ Bring it on ♪
♪ You can bang the drum You can bang the drum ♪
♪ You can bang the drum you can bang the drum ... ♪
- Is that Jake ? - Why is he here ?
I don 't know .
- We 're so busted . - No , he is .
I didn 't even catch any fish .
- JAKE : Slow down ! - Drew : Okay !
- Drew : I 'm doing what I can . - Careful , it 's not that deep .
We 're busted .
Okay , Jake , I 'm not taking the fall for this , it was all Zane 's idea .
I paid you 60 bucks to stay home , what do you mean ?
How about 40 and we call it even ?
How about you get on this boat and we go home , end of story ?
- Just get on the boat ! - Whoa , whoa .
We should have been at Canyon Beach an hour ago ,
- for the motherfucking main event ! - All right , go ahead , Speedo !
Be careful getting out of here , the rocks sometimes strip away the engine .
I want you to rest down here , okay ?
Keep Zane and Laura with you . I don 't want them anywhere near Derrick .
Wow , the water 's just so clear .
What kinda fish was that ?
I don 't know .
I 'm gonna make ' em take us home right now , okay ?
( Crash )
What is that ?
- Huh ! - KELLY : What happened ?
Are you guys okay ?
I think we hit something .
( Propeller grinding )
Andrew ! Andrew , what the hell is going on now ?
- I don 't know ! We 're stuck on something ! - Fix it , Goddamn it ! Fix it !
- There 's rocks everywhere . - There 's rocks down here .
What happened ?
There 's something caught on the prop .
- Stay put . - All right .
Crystal , get the sand rat up here .
I said , get the fucking sand rat up here ! Are you retarded ?
Why didn 't you go get him yourself ?
I 'm just out here thinking how this whole fucked-up day has been your fault .
You won 't help me with the new bitch .
You don 't do a fucking thing I tell you .
You take us way the fuck off course !
I ...
I get it , you 're ... you 're new at this .
I 'm cool with that , man . Really , I am ,
but what you 're doing to me ... what this is ...
God , there 's a word for it .
It 's uh ... It 's uh ...
It 's a boat word . What is it ? Uh ...
Mutiny .
Is that what this is ? Is this a mutiny ?
Look , relax , Derrick , okay , I 'm just ... I 'm just going a little wild .
Derrick !
If anyone should be down there helping , it ought to be you .
( Scraping noise )
Let me do that , let me do that ! Come on , let me do it .
( Propeller grinding )
- ( Loud music ) - This is an emergency .
I need everybody out of the water now !
Get out of the water . It 's an emergency . Get out of the water now !
Out of the water ! Get to your boat , right away .
- ( Loud music ) - ( Cheering )
( Loud music continues )
( Gasps )
- ( Screams ) - Shark ! Shark !
Who the fuck yells " shark " in a lake ? Oh , shit !
( Screaming )
Help ! Aargh !
Get the fuck out of the water !
( Screaming )
Come on ! Come on !
( Screams )
( Screaming )
( Creaking )
Oh , my God ! Oh , my God !
Aargh !
Oh , my God !
( Screaming )
Aargh !
- Oh ! - ( Screaming )
Oh , my God !
- Oh , my God , oh , my God ! - ( Screams )
( Screaming )
( Wailing )
Get in the boat !
What are you doing ?
JULIE : Where are you going ?
- Throw me the gun . - It 's fully loaded .
( Screaming )
- Get out of the water ! - Thank you .
Don 't let go .
Okay !
Swim to shore , get on the beach , get out of the water .
( Gunshots )
Help me , help me , gimme your hand .
Fucking help me , you fucking whore ! Help me !
Aargh !
Ah !
( Gunshots )
- Get them out of the water ! - Too many of them !
( Sobs ) They 're everywhere !
Come on ! I 'm taking you to shore ! Hold on !
There aren 't enough boats !
Aargh !
Todd , what are you doing ?
( Screaming )
Get the fuck outta the way !
Oh , shit ! Get the fuck outta the way !
Oh !
Fuck off !
- ( Screams ) - Oh , shit !
Let me go !
Stop the boat !
( Screams )
( Grinding )
Aargh !
( Propeller grinding )
-
DERRICK : Come on ! - Oh !
Derrick , hey , come on , you 're gonna kill the engine .
DERRICK : Come on !
Derrick , hey !
Zane , Laura , hold onto something .
Get back from the glass , you guys .
Ohh !
Come on ! Come on !
Come on ! Yeah . Yeah !
Yeah ! ( Laughs )
Oh !
Move !
No !
- ( Screams ) - Oh !
Argh !
Wah !
What the hell ?
( Groans )
Holy shit !
Aargh ! Aargh ! Aargh !
Oh , my God !
( Howls )
Go ! It 's okay !
Are you guys okay ?
- You okay ? - Yeah .
- Where 's Kelly ? - She 's on the other side !
Kelly ? Kelly ?
Jake !
Kelly , get off the floor , Kelly , get up !
I 'm gonna find a way to you ! I 'm gonna get to you through the skylight !
Hurry up !
Aargh ! Aargh !
Aargh ! Aargh ! Aargh !
Come on , you stupid bitch , come on !
Aargh !
( Shrieking )
Jake !
( Derrick howls )
Aargh ! Aargh !
Don 't let go !
( Screams , howls )
- Jake , Jake ! - Jake !
Okay , guys , come on , get over there , I don 't want you to see this .
( Derek groaning )
( Moans ) Jake !
Jake , they took my penis ! They took my penis !
Aargh ! Aargh ! Aargh !
Jake , hurry up , the water 's getting higher !
KELLY : Jake !
Kelly !
- Hurry up ! - Can you reach the skylight ?
( Screams )
Jake , ahh !
Open the glass .
- What are you doing ? - ( Grunts )
Jake ! ( Screams )
( Sobs )
( Burps )
( Moaning )
I got you !
( Screaming )
Everybody in !
Relax , we 're taking you to shore .
( Screams )
You 're gonna be all right ! Look at me ! Don 't look at it ! Don 't look at it !
Oh , shit !
( Starts engine )
( Grunts )
Chew on this , motherfuckers !
Everybody get out !
- ( Screams ) - Get out !
Everybody , get to the shore ! Get to the shore !
Aargh !
Aargh , aargh ! Aargh !
Everyone out !
Aargh ! Aargh !
Everybody out ! Everybody out !
No !
No , no ! ( Sobs )
( Phone rings )
Hold this tight .
This is Sheriff Forester .
- Mom ? - Jake !
I 'm so sorry , I screwed up , we 're on the lake .
What ? Where are Laura and Zane ?
They 're with me on the boat .
Oh , my God , Jake ! Whatever you do , do not go into the water .
You don 't understand , Mom , our boat is sinking .
What ?
Where are you ?
What are you doing ?
I 'm coming with you .
Let 's go .
That 's Mom .
Mom ! Hey !
- They 're stuck in the rocks . - Yeah .
- How we gonna get the boat close ? - I don 't know .
The rope . Here , you think it 'll reach ?
It 's got to . Jake ! I 'm gonna throw you the rope , attach it to the highest railing .
Okay , Mom .
- Back it up . - Yeah .
Back it up this way .
Watch out for the rocks .
Watch out !
Are you ready ?
Yeah .
That 's good , don 't come too far .
Yeah !
Shit ! Shit !
Keep the CB on the police frequency . I 've got my radio .
Okay , just get there .
LAURA : Mom ! Mom !
Mom , are you okay ?
I 'm sorry .
Is this everybody on the boat ?
No , Kelly 's still stuck in the cabin . We can 't get her out .
- What ? Oh , God ! Kelly ? - We can 't get her out !
Oh ! Julie !
Oh , I 'm gonna die !
- You gotta help me ! - Can you grab my arm ?
Help me ! The water 's getting higher !
- Can you reach the skylight ? - It doesn 't matter , it 's fucking stuck !
- You think I didn 't try to pry it up ? - God damn it !
Jake ! You guys ! I 'm scared !
Please help !
LAURA : Mom , we have to hurry !
Kelly ? Kelly !
Zane : Are we all gonna die ? JAKE : We 're not gonna die .
( Squeals )
Ah ! Fuck !
I need your help ! Please ! Jake !
The only way to get to her is through the bottom of the boat . Get to the rope .
What are you talking about ? We can 't leave her down there .
Once I get everyone across on the rope , I 'm gonna come back for her .
I 'm not gonna leave without her , Mom !
The only way to get to her is for you to get into the water . I 'm not gonna let you do that .
Get on the rope !
The reason she came on this boat was because of me .
It 's my fault .
I 'm not gonna leave without her .
NOVAK : This rope 's not gonna hold much longer , let 's go !
I 'm gonna take Zane and Laura across and then I 'm coming back ,
- and we are gonna do it together . - All right .
We 're gonna keep the two little ones between us . You 're gonna go first .
Can you do this ?
You better believe it . I don 't pole dance for nothing .
You have a lot of explaining to do .
You ready ?
Okay , be careful ! Don 't look down ! Let 's go !
- Hold on tight , Laura . - Mom !
Oh !
Right , just like at the playground , guys ... hand over hand .
Don 't look down .
- Don 't look down , all right ? - You guys are doing great .
Mom !
Keep going , come on , you can do it . Hand over hand .
I 'm scared !
- JULIE : Do not look down . - Mom !
JAKE : Keep going !
NOVAK : Careful !
JULIE : Don 't look down , okay ? Hold on !
JAKE : Come on , guys , you can do this ! Don 't look down !
( Danni squeals ) It bit me ! Go back ! Go back !
( Screams )
Get off me ! Get off me !
Get off ! ( Screams )
I 'm bleeding , I 'm bleeding !
( Screams ) Get off !
No , no , no !
( Screams )
Goddamn it !
Laura , listen to me .
Listen to me , both of you .
If you move fast , they will not get you .
You have to move now ! Come on , move it ! You can do it . Go !
NOVAK : Keep going now !
Mom !
- Mom ! - Mom !
JUNE : Keep going !
Okay , guys . Guys , you 're here .
Oh , you guys did it !
( Screams )
Dammit !
( Screams ) Oh !
JAKE : Come on , Mom , keep moving !
JAKE : You okay ?
Cut the engine !
JULIE : What are you doing ?
Jake , what are you doing ?
What are you doing ?
Jake ! Jake , do not do that .
Piranha want blood , right ? Let 's give it to ' em .
Argh !
Wet T-shirt .
( Grunts )
What the hell am I doing ?
( Boat creaking )
Jake !
Oh , my God ! Oh , my God !
We 're getting out of here , both of us .
Okay , I 'm in . I need you guys to pull us out as fast as possible . Do you copy ?
Okay , we 're ready when you are .
Okay .
Jake , what are you doing ? They 're gonna come back .
No , I gave ' em a snack . That 's gonna hold ' em off for at least a couple of minutes .
Okay , yes , yes ! Okay .
- I need you to tie these together . - Why ?
- Just do it ! - Jake , where you going ?
KELLY : Jake ?
- Okay . - Oh , my God .
You have them tied ? Come on .
Okay ... I need you to hold your breath ,
and we 're gonna swim out through the bottom of the boat , okay ?
I need you to hold on tight . Can you hold on tight to me ?
All right .
You 're clear to pull us out in ten seconds , okay ? Do you guys copy ?
Copy that . Ten seconds on your signal .
Get the kids down .
Ten .
( Both ) Six , five ,
four , three ,
two , one .
( Engine starts , fails )
- Um ... - What 's wrong ?
- Come on ! - I 'll check the prop .
- It 's clear . Is it in gear ? - God damn it !
No . Come on !
Come on , fucking thing !
Come on ! It 's gotta work , it 's gotta work !
Come on !
- ( Engine starts ) - ( Laughs )
( Explosion )
Oh , my God !
Holy shit !
- Jake ! - Kelly !
Are you all right ?
Kick your legs , come on !
- Oh , God ! - Come on !
Come on , you 're all right , you 're all right . Breathe , you 're okay .
- You 're okay . - ( Coughs )
You 're okay , you 're okay . Oh , my God !
Glad to have you on board . Jesus Christ .
- I 'm sorry , Mom . I 'm so sorry . - Holy shit !
Zane : Look , Mom , over there .
LAURA : My God !
LAURA : They 're all dead .
You did it , Jake .
I did . It worked .
I thought dynamite fishing was illegal in these parts , sheriff .
( CARL , ON RADIO ) Sheriff ? Sheriff ?
Yeah , this is Julie .
Julie , this is Carl . We have a major problem .
JULIE : I 'm looking out at a school of dead piranha .
It 's not all of them , but I think we 've got a good start .
CARL : You don 't understand .
The specimen you left with me , it has no mature reproductive organs .
- What ? - What are you talking about ?
The piranhas that killed those divers , the ones you 're hunting for ,
they 're not fully developed .
They 're the babies .
The babies ?
Huh .
So , where are the parents ?